Guide to the Gordon Moore Papers M1965
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2: Chronological Files, 1958-2003
  - Sub-Series I: Correspondence, Minutes and Other Material affiliated with Gordon Moore, 1958-2003
    - Intel Corp. M-4 Role of a Senior Manager Workshop - Correspondence, Presentation Slides re: Managing Our Cyclical Business, Articles, Corporate Business Indicators Summary, Overhead Transparencies, Course Instruction Guides [Originally in Box 30, Folder 6], April-August 1985 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Intel Corp. Technical Systems Symposium for Customers, Oregon - Notes, Program, Correspondence [Originally in Box 31, Folder 1], May 1985 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - LFRUT European Investors Meetings - Notes, Overhead Transparencies, Agenda, Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 31, Folder 2], June 1985 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - University of California, Santa Barbara Commencement Address - Speech [Originally in Box 31, Folder 3], June 1985 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Intel Corp. Lead the Leaders - Overhead Transparencies, Presentation Slides re: Strategic Long Range Plan [Originally in Box 31, Folder 5], July 1985 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Intel Corp. M-4 Role of the Senior Manager at Intel Course - Managing Cyclical Business - Notes, Correspondence, Overhead Transparencies, Presentation Slides, Charts [Originally in Box 31, Folder 8], August 1985 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Intel Corp. Board of Directors Meeting - Agenda, Minutes, Capital Project Authorization, Overhead Transparencies, Presentation Slides, FAB IX Wafer Facility Tour [Originally in Box 31, Folder 9], September 1985 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Stanford Research Institute International Industrial Conference - Program [Originally in Box 31, Folder 10], September 1985 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - IEEE Congressional Seminar re: Protectionism and International Technological Competition, Washington - Correspondence, Overhead Transparencies, Notes, Presentation Slides re: Semiconductor Industry [Originally in Box 31, Folder 11], October 1985 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - LFRUT (L.F. Rothschild, Unterberg, Towbin) Managing Technology Change Investment Conference, Palm Springs - Notes re: Semiconductors Drive Technology Change Microprocessors, Correspondence, Program [Originally in Box 31, Folder 12], October 1985 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - American Society for Metals Award for Advancement of Research - Correspondence [Originally in Box 31, Folder 13], October 1985 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Intel Corp. Announcement of 80386 Microprocessor in Europe - Correspondence, Briefings, Photocopied Notes, Andrew Grove Presentation on 386 [Originally in Box 31, Folder 14], October 1985 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Tax Policy is Trade Policy Research Paper by Robert Noyce [Originally in Box 32, Folder 3], October 1985 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Robert Noyce Research Papers - Churchill Club Speech, Notes for Industrial Engineering Department at Stanford University, Deanza Speech re: Silicon Valley, “Toward a Brighter Future” Research Paper, “Trends, Issues, Technologies” Research Paper, Notes, “Solving Trade Problem with Japan” Research Paper, “Tax Policy is Trade Policy” Research Paper, News clipping, Articles [Originally in Box 32, Folder 4], 1985-1987 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Semiconductor Equipment and Materials Institute - First Japanese/American Trade Partners Conference, Maui- Brochure, Correspondence, Notes, Presentation Slides, Program, Graphs [Originally in Box 32, Folder 6], November 1985 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Michigan Technological University Commencement Address - “Challenge to High Technology”- Correspondence, Notes, Pamphlet [Originally in Box 32, Folder 7], November 1985 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Robert Noyce Presentation for Pacific Rim Conference re: Domestic Determinants of Domestic Policy [Originally in Box 32, Folder 9], December 1985 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Montgomery Securities Semiconductor Technology Conference - Correspondence, Brochure, Notes re: 1986: The Year of Recovery (? Or !) [Originally in Box 32, Folder 12], January 1986 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - IEEE Presentation Speech by Robert Noyce [Originally in Box 33, Folder 3], February 1986 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Utah State University - Robert Noyce Research Paper re: Trends, Issues, Technologies, Map. Brochure [Originally in Box 33, Folder 9], March 1986 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Brookings Institution Conference on Understanding Business Policy and Operations - Correspondence, Overhead Transparencies, Presentation Slides of Robert Noyce Talk [Originally in Box 34, Folder 2], April 1986 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory - Agenda, Presentation Slides and Research Paper by Robert Noyce re: Industrial Competitiveness and Research Dilemma, Journal of Japanese Trade Industry (Article Highlighted), Computer Science Research Computation and Information Services Directorate, Research Paper by William G. Ouchi, Michele Kremen Bolton re: The Logic of Joint Research and Development [Originally in Box 34, Folder 13], August 1986 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Intel Corp. Board of Directors Meeting - Transcript Court Case with NEC Electronics, Strategic Long Range Plan, Minutes, Agenda, Correspondence, Overhead Transparencies, Capital Project Authorizations, Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 35, Folder 4], September 1986 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Intel Corp. Notes, Presentation Slides re: Future of Microcommunications [Originally in Box 35, Folder 6], September 1986 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Intel Corp. Compaq Computer Corp. Announcement - Agenda, Speaker Outlines, Notes [Originally in Box 35, Folder 7], September 1986 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Intel Corp. Korea/Japan Trip - Report on 8086 Microde Dispute with NEC Electronics, Itineraries, Expense Reports, Agendas, Articles, Correspondence re: Matsushita Electric Industrial Co. (MEI), Osaka Titanium Co. Ltd., Fujitsu, Melco, NEC Electronics, Toshiba, Mitsubishi Bank, Nissan, Samsung, Presentation Slides re: Changing Semiconductor Industry, US/Japan Trade Agreement Reports [Originally in Box 35, Folder 8], September-October 1986 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Intel Corp. Robert Noyce Research Paper re: Keeping California Competitive in R&D [Originally in Box 35, Folder 9], October 1986 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Fortune Magazine with Gordon Moore interview [Originally in Box 35, Folder 10], September 1986 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Dataquest Semiconductor Industry Conference, San Diego Binder - Program, Presentation Slides and Summaries (1 of 3) [Originally in Box 36, Folder 1], October 1986 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Dataquest Semiconductor Industry Conference, San Diego Binder - Program, Presentation Slides and Summaries (2 of 3) [Originally in Box 36, Folder 2], October 1986 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Dataquest Semiconductor Industry Conference, San Diego Binder - Program, Presentation Slides and Summaries (3 of 3) [Originally in Box 36, Folder 3], October 1986 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Dataquest Industry Briefing re: The 80386: Its Impact on the Computer Industry - Background Information on Intel’s Inboard 386/AT, Program, Correspondence, Notes re: The 80386 and Future of Computing, Presentation Slides, Solutions Special 32-Bit Issue 1985 [Originally in Box 36, Folder 4], October 1986 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Intel Corp. Distributor Presidents Conference - Presentation Slides, Agenda, Overhead Transparencies, Correspondence [Originally in Box 36, Folder 6], October 1986 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - University of California Irvine Dedication of Information and Computer Science/Engineering Research Facility - Program, Robert Noyce Speech Outline, Correspondence [Originally in Box 36, Folder 7], November 1986 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - MIT Enterprise Forum re: Entrepreneurship - Correspondence, Robert Noyce Speech Outline [Originally in Box 36, Folder 8], November 1986 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Intel Corp. Visit to Ford Electrical and Electronics Division and Electronic Data Systems Corp. - Agendas, Pamphlet, Correspondence [Originally in Box 37, Folder 1], November 1986 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Intel Corp. Board of Directors Meeting - Agenda, Minutes, Correspondence, Capital Project Authorizations, Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 37, Folder 2], November 1986 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Senate Budget and Fiscal Review Committee Retreat - Research Paper by Robert Noyce re: Competing in an Open Economy, Correspondence, Program, Agendas [Originally in Box 37, Folder 5], January 1987 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Intel Corp. Analysts Meeting – Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 37, Folder 8], January 1987 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Intel Corp. Trilateral Commission - Andrew Grove Speaker Notes [Originally in Box 37, Folder 14], March 1987 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Intel Corp. Industrial Research Institute - Research Paper by Robert Noyce re: Federal Laboratories Our Hidden Resource [Originally in Box 37, Folder 15], March 1987 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Intel People’s Republic of China Corp. - Correspondence re: China Microprocessor User’s Group Conference 1987, Articles, Background Information about China, Notes, Presentation Outlines (1 of 3) [Originally in Box 38, Folder 1], March 1987 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Intel People’s Republic of China Corp - Correspondence, Notes, Trip Report to the Peoples Republic of China (1988), Agendas, Articles (2 of 3) [Originally in Box 38, Folder 2], 1987 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Intel Corp. Capital Group - Presentation Notes [Originally in Box 38, Folder 4], April 1987 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Intel Corp. Annual Shareholders Meeting - Presentation Slides for Gordon Moore, Andrew Grove, Notes, Correspondence, Transcript of Meeting [Originally in Box 38, Folder 6], April 1987 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Intel Corp. AT&T Meetings - Correspondence, Article, Presentation Slides re: We are Driving Standards in 4 Strategic Areas [Originally in Box 38, Folder 10], May 1987 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Arizona World Trade Council - Robert Noyce Speech re: Toward a New Trade Policy: Balanced Trade [Originally in Box 39, Folder 1], May 1987 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Intel Corp. Visit to LME (Lars Magnus Ericsson) and Ericsson Information Systems (EIS) - Agenda, Correspondence, Overhead Transparencies [Originally in Box 39, Folder 2], May 1987 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Intel Corp. NTVA (Norges Tekniske Vitenskapsakademi) Norwegian Academy of Technical Sciences Conference re: New Electronic Materials and Components - Correspondence, Agenda, Notes re: The Rise and Fall of Silicon Valley, Andrew Grove Speaker Notes re: Silicon Valley, Presentation Slides, Pamphlets [Originally in Box 39, Folder 3], May 1987 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Santa Clara University Lecture re: Leadership in Science and Technology - Correspondence, Notes, Article [Originally in Box 39, Folder 4], June 1987 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - National Financial Computer and Automation Conference - Notes re: Technology of the 1990’s: Its Impact on the Financial Industry, Correspondence re: Securities Industry Automation Corporation (SIAC), Agenda, News Releases re: 386-based Microcomputer System, Article, Pamphlets, SIAC Annual Review 1986, New York Stock Exchange Annual Report 1986 [Originally in Box 39, Folder 8], July 1987 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Sandia Labs Speech by Robert Noyce re: Economy and Industrial Competitiveness in 1990s [Originally in Box 39, Folder 9], September 1987 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Intel Corp. Orange County Breakfast - Correspondence, Research Paper re: Semiconductor Industry Today by Robert Noyce [Originally in Box 39, Folder 10], September 1987 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Intel Corp. Distributor Presidents Conference - Briefing Package, Overhead Transparencies, Presentation Slides, Agenda [Originally in Box 39, Folder 11], October 1987 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Dataquest Semiconductor Industry Conference: Midlife Crisis Binder - Program, Newsletters, Report, Program, Presentation Slides and Summaries (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 40, Folder 1], October 1987 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Dataquest Semiconductor Industry Conference: Midlife Crisis Binder - Presentation Slides and Summaries (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 40, Folder 2], October 1987 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Dataquest Semiconductor Industry Conference: Midlife Crisis - Brochures, Presentation Slides re: Technology Begins at Forty, Presentation Slides re: Future of Very Large Scale Integration by Craig Barrett, Speech, Notes, Graphs, Article, Correspondence, Agenda [Originally in Box 40, Folder 3], October 1987 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Intel Corp. Q3 Analyst Meeting - Correspondence, Overhead Transparencies [Originally in Box 40, Folder 5], October 1987 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign Beckman Lecture Series - Notes, Correspondence, Presentation Slides re: From Grains of Sand, View of Semiconductor Industry, Booklet, Transcripts, Newspaper (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 40, Folder 6], November 1987 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign Beckman Lecture Series - Newsletters, Correspondence, Pamphlets, University of Illinois Office for Information Management Annual Reports (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 40, Folder 7], November 1987 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Intel Corp. Draft of Article re: Outlook for Computer Industry in 1988 for Computer Systems News, Perspective [Originally in Box 41, Folder 1], November 1987 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - American Electronics Association/Peat Marwick Seminar Series - Research Paper by Robert Noyce re: Competitiveness in US Technology Industry, Booklet [Originally in Box 41, Folder 2], November 1987 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Semiconductor Industry Association Long Range Planning Conference - Correspondence, Research Paper by Robert Noyce re: Restoring the Balance, Notes [Originally in Box 41, Folder 4], December 1987 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Intel Corp. Progress Reports - Correspondence re: Compensation Committee, Retirement Age, General Motors, Board of Directors Meeting (1995), Executive Compensation, Corporate Governance, CEO’s Guide to Maximizing the Effectiveness of the Board Pamphlet, Board Candidate Information [Originally in Box 41, Folder 6], 1988-1995 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Intel Corp. PCEO Personal Computer Enhancement Group 87 Executive Bonus - Overhead Transparencies, Correspondence, Notes, Charts, Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 41, Folder 7], January 1988 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Intel Corp. Correspondence, Article re: The Microprocessor: A Force for Change in Electronic Engineering [Originally in Box 41, Folder 9], March 1988 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Intel Corp. Technical Briefing/Big Bang Press Conference re: Embedded Control Products - Pamphlet, Correspondence, Notes, Agenda, Presentation Slides (from National Financial Computer and Automation Conference) [Originally in Box 41, Folder 10], April 1988 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - IEEE International Reliability Physics Symposium - Ribbon, Notes, Booklets, Correspondence, Presentation Slides re: It Doesn’t Get Any Easier: Some Semiconductor Industry Trends [Originally in Box 42, Folder 1], April 1988 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Intel Corp. Annual Shareholders Meeting, Albuquerque – Presentation Slides, Notes, Correspondence, Agendas, Minutes, Overhead Transparencies, Capital Project Authorizations, Form 10-K Annual Report, Article [Originally in Box 42, Folder 2], April 1988 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Caltech Lecture Series on Future Trends in Microcomputing - Notes re: It Doesn’t Get Any Easier: Some Semiconductor Industry Trends, Correspondence, Pamphlet, Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 42, Folder 4], May 1988 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Intel Corp. Vice President George Bush Visit to Oregon - Speech by Robert Noyce [Originally in Box 42, Folder 5], May 1988 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Intel Corp. Visit to Japan - Agenda, Correspondence, Overhead Transparencies, Notes, Presentation Slides re: Microcomputer Company: 20 Years of Progress [Originally in Box 42, Folder 6], May 1988 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Intel Corp. Board of Directors Meeting - Correspondence, Overhead Transparencies, Capital Project Authorizations, Agenda, Minutes [Originally in Box 42, Folder 9], June 1988 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Intel Corp. Presentation Slides re: Intel’s 20th Anniversary Agenda [Originally in Box 42, Folder 11], July 1988 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Intel Corp. Celebration of 20th Anniversary - Notes, Playbill re: Twenty Years Strong [Originally in Box 43, Folder 1], July 1988 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - National Academy of Engineers Founders Award - Presentation Slides, Notes re: Crisis in a Critical Industry - Microelectronics, Identification Card, Articles, Correspondence, Brochure (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 43, Folder 3], September 1988 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - National Academy of Engineers Founders Award - Brochures, Notes, Program, NAE Annual Meeting Issue (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 43, Folder 4], September 1988 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Intel Corp. Technology Conference, Oregon - Presentation Slides re: It Doesn’t Get Any Easier: Some Semiconductor Industry Trends, Notes [Originally in Box 43, Folder 5], October 1988 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Intel Corp. Technology Conference, Oregon - Digest of Technical Papers [Originally in Box 173], October 1988 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Intel Corp. DVI (Digital Video Interactive) Technology Announcement - Correspondence, Press Releases, Notes, Research Papers [Originally in Box 43, Folder 6], October 1988 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Digital Equipment Corporation (DEC) Meeting re: Technology Exchange Institute for Engineering Deans - Correspondence, Booklets, Agenda [Originally in Box 43, Folder 7], October 1988 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology Club of Northern California re: Dialogue with a CEO, Robert Noyce - Correspondence, Notes, Overhead Transparencies, Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 43, Folder 8], November 1988 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Intel Corp. Executive Correspondence with Andrew Grove, Craig Barrett, Gordon Moore, Presentation Slides, Memo Notepads (1 of 3) [Originally in Box 44, Folder 3], 1988-1990 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Intel Corp. Executive Correspondence with Andrew Grove, Craig Barrett, Gordon Moore re: Finances, Corporate Objectives, Presentation Slides, Agendas, Notes (3 of 3) [Originally in Box 44, Folder 5], 1995-1997 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - National Academy of Engineering Profiting from Innovation Workshop re: Organizing for Success - Overhead Transparencies, Correspondence, Presentation Slides, Agenda, Notes re: Function versus Project Organization, Program [Originally in Box 45, Folder 2], January 1989 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Intel Corp. i860 Microprocessor Announcement - Press Releases, Notes [Originally in Box 45, Folder 5], February 1989 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - IEEE Computer Society International Conference (Compcon 89) and Caltech Very Large Scale Integration Conference (March) - Presentation Slides, Correspondence, Program [Originally in Box 45, Folder 6], February 1989 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Decennial Caltech Conference on Very Large Scale Integration - Notes, Correspondence, Presentation Slides re: It Doesn’t Get Any Easier, Some VLSI Industry Trends, Agenda, Program [Originally in Box 45, Folder 8], March 1989 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Intel Corp. Design Conference - Correspondence, Digest of Technical Papers, Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 46, Folder 1], March 1989 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Intel Corp. i486 Microprocessor Announcement - Presentation Slides, Correspondence, Press Releases, Notes [Originally in Box 46, Folder 4], April 1989 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - National Nanofabrication Facility at Cornell University Policy Board Meeting at Sandia National Laboratories - Correspondence, Map, Minutes, Agenda [Originally in Box 46, Folder 5], April 1989 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - In-Stat, Inc. Annual Semiconductor Forum re: 1990’s: The Next Generation Binder - Agendas, Presentation Slides and Summaries (1 of 3) [Originally in Box 46, Folder 7], April 1989 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - In-Stat, Inc. Annual Semiconductor Forum re: 1990’s: The Next Generation Binder - Agendas, Presentation Slides and Summaries (2 of 3) [Originally in Box 46, Folder 8], April 1989 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - In-Stat, Inc. Annual Semiconductor Forum re: 1990’s: The Next Generation -Correspondence, Notes, Presentation Slides re: Perspectives of the Future, Programs, Brochure (3 of 3) [Originally in Box 47, Folder 1], April 1989 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - National Research Council Panel re: Keeping the US Computer Industry Competitive - Correspondence, Agendas, Pamphlets, Notes, Research Paper [Originally in Box 47, Folder 3], May 1989 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Semiconductor Industry Association/Semiconductor Equipment & Materials Institute Ad Hoc Meeting - Correspondence, Presentation Slides, Agendas [Originally in Box 47, Folder 4], May 1989 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - University of California, Berkeley Commencement Address re: Changing World of Science and Technology - Correspondence, Notes, Research paper [Originally in Box 47, Folder 5], May 1989 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Intel Corp. IJKK (Intel Kabushiki Kaisha) Japan Meeting - Notes, Overhead Transparencies, Correspondence, Newspaper, Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 47, Folder 6], June 1989 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Stanford Research Institute/Japan-Western US Association Panel re: High Tech Relations with Japan - Correspondence, Presentation Slides, Research Papers, American Magazine 1989 Issue [Originally in Box 47, Folder 8], July 1989 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Semiconductor Industry Association Statement Represented by Gordon Moore - Testifying Anti-Trust before House Judiciary Subcommittee on Economic and Commercial Law [Originally in Box 47, Folder 9], July 1989 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Intel Corp. IBM Meeting - Research Papers, Correspondence, Presentation Slides, Notes [Originally in Box 48, Folder 1], August 1989 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology Very Large Scale Integration Seminar - Notes, Correspondence, Forms, Presentation Slides re: VLSI Industry Trends, Technological and Economic [Originally in Box 48, Folder 2], September 1989 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Semiconductor Industry Association Annual Industry Conference re: Sharpening the Competitive Edge Binder - Agendas, Notes, Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 48, Folder 3], September 1989 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - American Electronics Association Oregon Council Meeting - Presentation Slides re: Can the US Companies Compete in Semiconductors?, Speech Outline, Booklets re: America’s Future at Stake: Winning in the Global Marketplace, Notes, Correspondence, Brochure [Originally in Box 48, Folder 6], September 1989 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Intel Corp. Board of Directors Meeting - Agenda, Presentation Slides, Overhead Transparencies, Correspondence, Capital Project Authorizations [Originally in Box 48, Folder 7], September 1989 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Semiconductor Industry Association Annual Industry Conference re: Global Competition, Global Partnership Binder - Agendas, Notes, Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 49, Folder 2], September 1990 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Intel Corp. UK Fair - Correspondence, Brochure, Presentation Slides, Speech Outline, Notes [Originally in Box 49, Folder 3], October 1989 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Associates of the Caltech Annual Dinner - Speech Outline re: Computer Chip- Keystone of Modern Electronics, Notes, Correspondence, Presentation Slides, Presentation Outline for University of Illinois [Originally in Box 49, Folder 5], 1987 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Intel Corp. Distributor Presidents Conference - Presentation Slides, Notes, Correspondence [Originally in Box 49, Folder 7], October 1989 (Box 21, Folder 5)